This potential neck opening, is not someone with a napkin, tied around their neck in order to eat dinner.
She's not going to eat any barbecue anytime soon.
But, this is an opening that has knotted shoulders.
The point of this is to create variation in your styles.
You can flip it upside-down and have the knots at the bottom if you wanted to.
What the knotted shoulders show you, is that there's two, the knots can either be faux knots, that are placed there and then have it sewn closed or you could actually have the garment go on, kind of, I guess kind of like a diaper.
But a top.
And there's, your front piece is one piece, and then your back piece is another piece.
And they come up over the shoulders and tie together.
That's how the garment stays on.
That's why it looks kind of like a napkin, around your neck.
But the knots, right there, are created by bunching a wider, width of fabric into a smaller width and then you have your knots.